export default data4 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "Who was the first person to sail single-handed around the world without stopping?",
        options: ["Sir Francis Drake", "Dame Ellen MacArthur", "Sir Robin Knox-Johnston", "Sir Francis Chichester"],
        correct_option: "Sir Robin Knox-Johnston"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "When does Easter take place?",
        options: ["November or December", "January or February", "March or April", "May or June"],
        correct_option: "March or April"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "Where is the Eden Project located?",
        options: ["Dorset", "Cornwall", "Devon", "Somerset"],
        correct_option: "Cornwall"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "St Helena and the Falkland Islands are part of Great Britain.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "Where should you register if you want to become part of a jury?",
        options: ["The electoral register", "Your local church", "The NHS", "The British Embassy"],
        correct_option: "The electoral register"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "What sort of church is the Church of Scotland?",
        options: ["Catholic", "Baptist", "Presbyterian", "Methodist"],
        correct_option: "Presbyterian"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "Where does golf come from?",
        options: ["Wales", "Australia", "Ireland", "Scotland"],
        correct_option: "Scotland"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "When do the television and newspapers have stories that are jokes until midday?",
        options: ["Valentine’s Day", "Boxing Day", "Halloween", "April Fool’s Day"],
        correct_option: "April Fool’s Day"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "What king was defeated by Oliver Cromwell during the Civil War and hid in an oak tree before escaping to Europe?",
        options: ["Richard III", "Charles II", "James I", "Henry IV"],
        correct_option: "Charles II"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "Who was the father of Queen Elizabeth I?",
        options: ["Edward I", "Henry V", "Henry VII", "Henry VIII"],
        correct_option: "Henry VIII"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "Who is the patron Saint of Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["St George", "St Patrick", "St Andrew", "St David"],
        correct_option: "St Patrick"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "What is the name of the period when new ideas about politics, philosophy and science were developed?",
        options: ["The Enlightenment", "The Glorious Revolution", "The Swinging Sixties", "The Reformation"],
        correct_option: "The Enlightenment"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "In which battle did Admiral Nelson die?",
        options: ["The Battle of Hastings", "The Battle of Waterloo", "The Battle of Trafalgar", "The Battle of Bannockburn"],
        correct_option: "The Battle of Trafalgar"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "What sort of charity is ‘Friends of the Earth’?",
        options: ["An environmental charity", "A medical research charity", "A charity working with pets", "A charity working with older people"],
        correct_option: "An environmental charity"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "In which country of the British Empire did the Boer War (1899-1902) take place?",
        options: ["Netherlands", "Falkland Islands", "Gibraltar", "South Africa"],
        correct_option: "South Africa"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "Which novel written by JRR Tolkien was voted the country’s best-loved novel in 2003?",
        options: ["Oliver Twist", "James Bond", "Pride and Prejudice", "The Lord of the Rings"],
        correct_option: "The Lord of the Rings"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "When did Germany invade Poland?",
        options: ["1942", "1941", "1940", "1939"],
        correct_option: "1939"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "How were Elizabeth I and ‘Mary, Queen of Scots’ related?",
        options: ["They were cousins", "They were sisters", "They were mother and daughter", "They were not related"],
        correct_option: "They were cousins"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "What does the NATO stand for?",
        options: ["The North American Transparent Organisation", "The North Atlantic Trust Organisation", "The North Atlantic Treaty Organisation", "The North American Treaty Organisation"],
        correct_option: "The North Atlantic Treaty Organisation"
    },
     {
        id: "20",
        question: "What characterised the people from the Bronze Age?",
        options: ["They were accomplished metalworkers", "They were farmers who lived in large villages", "They were nomads and hunters", "They were divided into clans"],
        correct_option: "They were accomplished metalworkers"
    },
     {
        id: "21",
        question: "Where is the National Horseracing Museum located?",
        options: ["In Newmarket, Suffolk", "In St Andrews, Scotland", "In Richmond, London", "In Aintree, near Liverpool"],
        correct_option: "In Newmarket, Suffolk"
    },
     {
        id: "22",
        question: "In which of the following matters the Scottish Parliament CANNOT legislate?",
        options: ["Health", "Education", "Immigration", "Planning"],
        correct_option: "Immigration"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Does Britain have a constitutional monarchy?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        correct_option: "Yes"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "Who defeated the French at the battle of Agincourt in 1415?",
        options: ["King Edward I of England", "William III of England", "Henry VIII", "King Henry V"],
        correct_option: "King Henry V"
    },

]